

# **My Contact**



P adityagita.github.io



🕅 adityamanggalagita@gmail.com



(in) adityamanggalagita



Banyuwangi, East Java

## **Hard Skill**

- Exploratory Data Analysis (EDA)
- Data Cleaning & Analysis

+62 811 369 6293

- Data Modeling
- Data Reporting

### Soft Skill

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Analytical thinking
- Problem-solving

#### Tools

- Spreadsheets/Excel
- **SQL** Google Bigguery
- **Google Colaboratory**
- **Looker Studio**
- Tableau

## **Education Background**

#### RevoU

Full Stack Data Analytics Program Jan 2022 - May 2022

- Responsible as Data Analyst for end-toend data analysis group project
- · Managed to enter Top 3 in a final group project with video games sales analysis
- Selected as one of the top students to work as Section Manager for the next
- Final Score 97.33/100

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember (ITS) Bachelor of Chemical Engineering

2011 - 2016

- · Final thesis about the electrodeposition of hydroxyapatite composite on bone implant metal coating
- Cumulative GPA 3.14/4.00

# ADITYA MANGGALA GITA

Aspiring Data Analyst

#### **About Me**

An aspiring data analyst with a chemical engineering background who wants to be an expert in data analytics and loves to help others to make an impact. Reliable, agile in a fast-paced environment. After two years of working with data in a government institution, I found my passion for the data analytics field. Recently graduated from the highly selective (acceptance rate < 10%) Full-Stack Data Analytics program at RevoU in which I got to learn end-to-end data analytics processes. A confident and passionate person who has an appetite for new challenges and continually learns new skills.

## **Professional Experience**

#### PT Revolusi Cita Edukasi (RevoU) | Section Manager May 2022 - December 2022

- · Leading and moderating live classes for two batches consisting of 138 students.
- Maintaining the quality of all stakeholders that consist of students, team leads, and instructors to ensure high engagement and optimal learning process while improving class satisfaction rate from 4.75 in the first batch to 4.89 in the following batch
- Preparing regular reports of main performance KPIs and insights in order to provide recommendations and communicate improvement ideas to increase the efficiency and effectiveness of running the program batch

#### Dinas Lingkungan Hidup Banyuwangi | Waste **Management Staff**

Jan 2021 - April 2022

- Maintaining smooth collaboration with waste management stakeholders.
- Improving the waste management service system by adding data-driven decisions to estimate the usage of fuel.
- Creating reports on the disbursement of funds for waste management vehicle fuel.
- Monitoring the use of fuel for waste management vehicles to ensure compliance with allocated budgets

#### UPT Laboratorium Lingkungan Banyuwangi | **Chemical Analyst**

Jan 2018 - December 2020

- Conducting chemical analysis of wastewater samples to ensure compliance with existing quality standards
- Collecting wastewater samples according to established national standard operating procedures

## **Projects**

**Video Games** Sales Analysis Proposed actionable strategies for video games distributor company to increase revenue, catch up with changes in the gaming industry and sustain the business

Acted as Data Analyst and managed to get into top 3 of final project competition

**E-Commerce** Customer Segmentation

user segmentation marketing that fits the marketing budget of the company